Finding Aid for the John J. Bonica Papers Biomed.0118
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Publications
  - Curriculum Vitae Items.
    - Comparison of the cardiovascular and respiratory effects. CV Item 104, 1970. Can. Anaesth. Soc. J. 17:61-69 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 104)
    - Basic principles. CV Item 105, 1970. Management of intractable pain (Proceedings of the Fourth World Congress of. (Box 120, Folder 105)
    - Treatment of pain. CV Item 106, 1970. Jap. J. Anaesthesiol. 19:1-10. (Box 120, Folder 106)
    - Pain -- basic principles of management. CV Item 107, 1970. Northwest Med. 69:567-568. (Box 120, Folder 107)
    - Pain in the extremities. CV Item 108, 1970. Northwest Med. 69:570-571. (Box 120, Folder 108)
    - Current concepts of the pain process. CV Item 109, 1970. Northwest Med. 69:661-664. (Box 120, Folder 109)
    - Treatment of pain and nerve block. CV Item 110, 1970. Proceedings of the Symposium on Local and Conduction Anesthesia, pp. 55-64,. (Box 120, Folder 110)
    - Obstetric analgesia and anesthesia: Recent trends and. CV Item 111, 1970. New York State J. Med. 70:2079-2084. (Box 120, Folder 111)
    - Problems of aging: Nerve blocks for managing pain in the. CV Item 112, 1970. Postgrad. Med. 47:215-220. (Box 120, Folder 112)
    - Obstetric analgesia and anesthesia. CV Item 113, 1970. J. Obstet. Anesth. (Japan) 31:67-95. (Box 120, Folder 113)
    - Circulatory effects of peridural block: I. Effects of level of. CV Item 114, 1970. Anesthesiology 33:619-626. (Box 120, Folder 114)
    - Simultaneous systemic cardiovascular and renal. CV Item 115, 1970. Acta Anaesth. Scandinav. 37:163-171 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 115)
    - Influencia de la hemorragia aguda sobre los efectos. CV Item 116, 1970. Rev. Argent. Anesth. 28:23-27. (Box 120, Folder 116)
    - Obstetrisk analgesi i dag. CV Item 117, 1971. Svensk Lakartidn. 68:729-739. (Box 120, Folder 117)
    - Anestesia peridural segmentaria en el periodo de. CV Item 118, 1971. Revista Uruguaya de Anestesiologia 5:45-52. (Box 120, Folder 118)
    - Local anesthetics: Handle with care. CV Item 119, 1971. Consultant 11:48-51. (Box 120, Folder 119)
    - Circulatory effects of peridural block: II. Effects of. CV Item 120, 1971. Anesthesiology 34:514-522. (Box 120, Folder 120)
    - Regional analgesia-anesthesia in obstetrics: Nerve blocks. CV Item 121, 1971. Proceedings of the Third Asian and Australasian Congress of Anaesthesia, pp.. (Box 120, Folder 121)
    - The effects of methoxamine and ephedrine in. CV Item 122, 1971. Anesthesiology 35:354-361. (Box 120, Folder 122)
    - Oral analgesics for chronic pain. CV Item 123, 1971. Modern Medicine 39:87-93. (Box 120, Folder 123)
    - Circulatory effects of peridural block III. Effects of acute. CV Item 124, 1972. Anesthesiology 36:219-227 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 124)
    - Effect of pudendal, spinal, and peridural block anesthesia. CV Item 125, 1972. Am. J. Obstet. Gynnecol. 113:166-175. (Box 120, Folder 125)
    - Local anesthetics and regional anesthesia (Epitomies of. CV Item 126, 1972. Calif. Med. 117:48-49. (Box 120, Folder 126)
    - Transplacental passage of narcotics, narcotic. CV Item 127, 1972. (Proceedings of the Congres National d'Anesthesia, Paris, March 1972), pp.. (Box 120, Folder 127)
    - Management of chronic orthopaedic pain problems. CV Item 128, 1972. AAOS Instructional Course Lectures 21:8-22. (Box 120, Folder 128)
    - Operant conditioning for chronic pain. CV Item 129, 1974. Recent Advances on Pain, Pathophysiology and Clinical Aspects, (A Symposium),. (Box 120, Folder 129)
    - General clinical considerations (including organization. CV Item 130, 1974. Recent Advances on Pain, Pathophysiology and Clinical Aspects, (A Symposium), [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 130)
    - Maternal cardiovascular dynamics VI. Cesarean section. CV Item 131, 1972. Am. J. Obstet. Gynnecol. 114:775-780. (Box 120, Folder 131)
    - Managing chronic pain, (Interview). CV Item 132, 1972. Chronic Disease Management 6:2, 6-7. (Box 120, Folder 132)
    - Management of Chronic Pain. CV Item 133, 1973. (Symposium on Analgesics, Cornell University Medical College, April 1972), New. (Box 120, Folder 133)
    - Spinal anesthesia and ephedrine in pregnant monkeys. CV Item 134, 1973. Am. J. Obstet. Gynnecol. 115:109510993 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 134)
    - Fundamental considerations of chronic pain therapy. CV Item 135, 1973. Postgrad. Med. 53:81-85. (Box 120, Folder 135)
    - Analgesic blocks. CV Item 136, 1973. Postgrad. Med. 53:105-110. (Box 120, Folder 136)
    - Causalgia and other reflex sympathetic dystrophies. CV Item 137, 1973. Postgrad. Med. 53:143-148. (Box 120, Folder 137)
    - The total management of the patient with chronic pain,. CV Item 138, 1973. Drug Therapy 3:33-47. (Box 120, Folder 138)
    - Recent advances in the pathophysiology of pain. CV Item 139, 1973. Anaesthesiology (Proceedings of the Fifth World Congress of Anaesthesiologists,. (Box 120, Folder 139)
    - Circulatory effects of peridural block: IV. Comparison of. CV Item 140, 1973. Anesthesiology 39:308-314. (Box 120, Folder 140)
    - Cardiovascular side effects and complications of local. CV Item 141, 1974. Proceedings of the International Meeting of Anesthesiology and Resuscitation, pp. [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 141)
    - Organization and function of a pain clinic. CV Item 142, 1974. International Symposium on Pain, pp. 433-443, (Advances in Neurology, Vol. 4), New. (Box 120, Folder 142)
    - Current role of nerve blocks in the diagnosis and therapy of. CV Item 143, 1974. International Symposium on Pain, 445-453, (Advances in Neurology, Vol. 4), New. (Box 120, Folder 143)
    - Anesthesiology in the People's Republic of China. CV Item 144, 1974. Anesthesiology 40:175-186. (Box 120, Folder 144)
    - Spinal and extradural analgesia-anesthesia for parturition. CV Item 145, 1974. Clinical Obstetrics and Gynecology 17(2):183-198. (Box 120, Folder 145)
    - Experiences with the use of ketamine for parturition: I.. CV Item 146, 1974. Anesth. Analg. 53:2, 284-287. (Box 120, Folder 146)
    - Current status of pain clinics. CV Item 147, 1974. Interdisziplinare Schmerzbehandlung, pp. 84-95, Berlin, Springer. (Box 120, Folder 147)
    - Therapeutic acupuncture in the People's Republic of. CV Item 148, 1974. J.A.M.A. 228:1544-1551. (Box 120, Folder 148)
    - Acupuncture. CV Item 149, 1974. Encyclopedia Americana 1:132 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 149)
    - Acupuncture anesthesia in the People's Republic of. CV Item 150, 1974. J.A.M.A. 229:1317-1325. (Box 120, Folder 150)
    - Effect of acute hypovolemia on lignocaine absorption and. CV Item 151, 1974. Br. J. Anaesth. 46:631-635 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 151)
    - Pain: Its definition, its effects, and its mechanisms. CV Item 152, 1974. Mod. Med. 42:26-35 (September 16). (Box 120, Folder 152)
    - Why the patient suffers: Theories and concepts of pain. CV Item 153, 1974. Mod. Med. 42:56-63 (November 11). (Box 120, Folder 153)
    - How to learn why the patient hurts. Attacking the Puzzle of. CV Item 154, 1975. Mod. Med. 43:68-73 (January 15). (Box 120, Folder 154)
    - The pain clinic - new promise of relief for suffering. CV Item 155, 1975. Mod. Med. 43:52-59 (March 1). (Box 120, Folder 155)
    - The risks and benefits of cutting pain's pathways.. CV Item 156, 1975. Mod. Med. 43:74-87 (April 15). (Box 120, Folder 156)
    - Helping the patient unlearn the habit of pain. Attacking. CV Item 157, 1975. Mod. Med. 43:58-72 (September 1). (Box 120, Folder 157)
    - Quality of spinal extradural anaesthesia. The influence of. CV Item 158, 1975. Br. J. Anaesth. 47:41-47. (Box 120, Folder 158)
    - Maternal and fetal responses to halothane in pregnant. CV Item 159, 1975. Acta Anaesth. Scand. 19:154-158. (Box 120, Folder 159)
    - Experiences with the use of ketamine for parturition: I.. CV Item 160, 1975. Anesth. Analg. 53:284-287. (Box 120, Folder 160)
    - Respiratory function in pregnant obese women. CV Item 161, 1975. Am. J. Obstet. Gynnecol. 123:241-245 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 161)
    - Basic considerations, (Obstetric Analgesia-Anesthesia,. CV Item 162, 1975. Clin. Obstet. Gvnaecol. 2:469-497. (Box 120, Folder 162)
    - The Nature of pain of parturition. CV Item 163, 1975. Clin. Obstet. Gynaecol. 2:499-516. (Box 120, Folder 163)
    - General clinical considerations, (Obstetric. CV Item 164, 1975. Clin. Obstet. Gynaecol. 2:517-529. (Box 120, Folder 164)
    - General analgesia-anaesthesia for vaginal delivery. CV Item 165, 1975. Clin. Obstet. Gynaecol. 2:545-555 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 165)
    - Extradural analgesia-anaesthesia for labour and vaginal. CV Item 166, 1975. Clin. Obstet. Gynaecol. 2:593-608. (Box 120, Folder 166)
    - Diagnostic and therapuetic blocks in pain therapy. CV Item 167, 1975. Compr. Ther. 1(6):32-40. (Box 120, Folder 167)
    - Effects of peridural block: V. Properties, circulatory. CV Item 168, 1976. Anesthesiology 42:398-407 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 168)
    - Effects of extradural block. Comparison of properties,. CV Item 169, 1976. Br. J. Anaesth. 43:575-586. (Box 120, Folder 169)
    - Respiratory depression in newborn monkeys at cesarean. CV Item 170, 1976. Br. J. Anaesth. 47:917-9211. (Box 120, Folder 170)
    - A comparison of the effects of 4% and 8% fluoroxene in. CV Item 171, 1976. Acta Anaesth. Scand. 20:183-188. (Box 120, Folder 171)
    - Recent studies on the nature and management of acute. CV Item 172, 1976. Special Report, New York, Hospital Practice Publishing Company, January [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 172)
    - Hemodynamic drug interaction: Peridural lidocaine and. CV Item 173, 1976. Acta Anaesth. Scand. 20:207-210,. (Box 120, Folder 173)
    - The effects of adding adrenaline to etidocaine and. CV Item 174, 1976. Br. J. Anaesth. 48:893-898. (Box 120, Folder 174)
    - The effects of adding adrenaline to etidocaine and. CV Item 175, 1976. Br. J. Anaesth. 48:989-994. (Box 120, Folder 175)
    - Introduction to the First World Congress on Pain: Goals of. CV Item 176, 1976. Advances in Pain Research and Therapy, Vol. 1, pp. xxvii-xxxix, (Proceedings of the) [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 176)
    - Pain in labor: The causes and its relief and the effects of. CV Item 177, 1976. Self, Family, Society: Toward Freedom and Growth in Parenthood, pp. 142-158, [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 177)
    - Bloquelos nerviosos para diagnostics, terapeutica e. CV Item 178, 1976. Revista Brasileira de Anesthesiologia 26:599-615. (Box 120, Folder 178)
    - Mecanismos da dor. CV Item 179, 1976. Revista Brasileira de Anestesiologia 26:476-502. (Box 120, Folder 179)
    - Aspetti neurofisiologici e strutturali del dolore acuto e. CV Item 180, 1976. Recenti Progressi in Medinina 61:450-475. (Box 120, Folder 180)
    - Considerations in management of acute pain. CV Item 181, 1977. Hospital Practice (Special issue),. (Box 120, Folder 181)
    - Ketamine for obstetric delivery, (Correspondence). CV Item 182, 1977. Anesthesiology 46:78. (Box 120, Folder 182)
    - Effects of intrasegmental electrical acupuncture on dental. CV Item 183, 1977. Pain 3:213-227. (Box 120, Folder 183)
    - Introduction to Symposium on Pain. CV Item 184, 1977. Arch. Surg. 112:749. (Box 120, Folder 184)
    - Neurophysiologic and pathologic aspects of acute and. CV Item 185, 1977. Arch. Surg. 112:750-761. (Box 120, Folder 185)
    - Physiopathology and control of postoperative pain. CV Item 186, 1977. Arch. Surg. 112:773-781. (Box 120, Folder 186)
    - Basic principles in managing chronic pain. CV Item 187, 1977. Arch. Surg. 112:787-788 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 187)
    - Acupuncture analgesia and anesthesia. CV Item 188, 1977. Arch. Surg. 112:896-902 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 188)
    - Pain, depression, and illness behavior in pain clinic. CV Item 189, 1977. Pain 4:183-192 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 189)
    - Pathophysiology of pain. CV Item 190, 1978. Current Concepts in Postoperative Pain, pp. 4-14, (A symposium held in conjunction. (Box 120, Folder 190)
    - Maternal physiologic and psychologic alternations and. CV Item 191, 1978. Current Reviews for Nurse Anesthetists, Inc., Vol. 1, Lesson 11. (Box 120, Folder 191)
    - Chairman's introductory remarks, (Pain Panel). CV Item 192, 1978. (Proceedings of the VI World Congress of Anaesthesiology, Mexico City, April 24-30, [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 192)
    - Neurophysiologic and psychologic substrates of pain. CV Item 193, 1978. (Proceedings of the VI World Congress of Anesthesiology, Mexico City, April 24-30, [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 193)
    - Chronic Pain: Its importance and mechanisms. CV Item 194, 1978. (Proceedings of the VI World Congress of Anesthesiology, Mexico City, April 24-30, [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 194)
    - Cancer Pain. A major national health problem. CV Item 195, 1978. Cancer Nurs. J. 4:313-316. (Box 120, Folder 195)
    - Pain and the Anesthesiologist. CV Item 196, 1978. Acta. Anaesth. Scand. Suppl. 70:7-9 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 196)
    - Introduction. CV Item 197, 1979. Recent Advances in the Management of Acute and Chronic Pain, Hospital Practice,. (Box 120, Folder 197)
    - Importance of the problem. CV Item 198, 1979. Advances in Pain Research and Therapy, Vol. 2, pp. 1-12, (Proceedings of the. (Box 120, Folder 198)
    - Introduction to management of pain of advanced cancer. CV Item 199, 1979. Advances in Pain Research and Therapy, Vol. 2, pp. 115-130, (Proceedings of the [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 199)
    - Introduction to nerve blocks. CV Item 200, 1979. Advances in Pain Research and Therapy, Vol. 2, pp. 303-310, (Proceedings of the [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 200)
    - Cranial nerve blocks. CV Item 201, 1979. Advances in Pain Research and Therapy, Vol. 2, pp. 347-355, (Proceedings of the [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 201)
    - Cancer pain in the head and neck: Role of nerve blocks. CV Item 202, 1979. Advances in Pain Research and Therapy, Vol. 2, pp. 537-542, (Proceedings of the [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 202)
    - Important Clinical Aspects of Acute and Chronic Pain;. CV Item 203, 1979. Mechanisms of Pain and Analgesic Compounds, pp. 13-31; 97-105, New York, [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 203)
    - Causalgia and other reflex sympathetic dystrophies. CV Item 204, 1979. Advances in Pain Research and Therapy, Vol. 3, pp. 141-166, (Proceedings of the. (Box 120, Folder 204)
    - Illness behavior and depression compared in pain center. CV Item 205, 1979. Pain 6:1-7. (Box 120, Folder 205)
    - Peripheral mechanisms and pathways of parturition pain. CV Item 206, 1979. Br. J. Anaesth. 51:3-9 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 206)
    - Cardiovascular and subjective central nervous system. CV Item 207, 1979. Anaesth. Inten. Care 7:215-221 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 207)
    - Editorial: The need of a taxonomy. CV Item 208, 1979. Pain 6:247-252. (Box 120, Folder 208)
    - Aspetti basici e cliniche del dolore acuto e cronico. CV Item 209, 1979. Proceedings, Italian League Against Pain, Gubbio, Italy, December 7 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 209)
    - The relation of injury to pain. CV Item 210, 1979. Pain 7:203-207 [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 210)
    - Introduction. CV Item 211, 1979. Pain, pp. 1-17 (Conclusion, pp. 381-387), (Proceedings of the 58th Annual Meeting of. (Box 120, Folder 211)
    - Cancer pain. CV Item 212, 1979. Pain, pp. 337-362, (Proceedings of the 58th Annual Meeting of the association for. (Box 120, Folder 212)
    - Pain research and therapy: Past and current status and. CV Item 213, 1980. Pain, Discomfort and Humanitarian Care, (Proceedings of the NIH Conference on. (Box 120, Folder 213)
    - The anesthesiologist. CV Item 214, 1980. Pain Overview, 1980: The Management of Postoperative Pain, New York, HP. (Box 120, Folder 214)
    - Development and current status of anesthesiology. CV Item 215, 1980. Proceedings, Central European Congress of Anesthesiology, September 5-8, 1979, [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 215)
    - Pain and Stress. CV Item 216, 1981. Research in Stress in Health and Disease, (Report by Institute of Medicine, National [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 216)
    - Development and current status of anesthesiology. CV Item 217, 1981. Zentraleuropgischer AnaesthesiekongreB, Band 1, Anaesthesiologie und [folder is empty]. (Box 120, Folder 217)
    - Editorial, (Pain). CV Item 218, 1981. Triangle 20:1-6. (Box 120, Folder 218)
    - Cancer Pain. CV Item 219, 1981. Schmerz 3:67-87. (Box 120, Folder 219)
    - Postoperative Pain, (Symposium on Postoperative Pain at. CV Item 220, 1982. Contemp. Surg. 20(l):83-110 (Part 1, January); 20(2):119-152 (Part 2, February). (Box 120, Folder 220)
    - Management of Pain. CV Item 221, 1982. Schmerzstudien, (2. Offenen Schmer k@onferenz, June 13, 1981, Frankfurt). (Box 120, Folder 221)
    - Foreword. CV Item 222, 1982. Seminars in Anesthesia, (Obstetrics in Anesthesii)-, June 1982, Anesthesia 1(,2). (Box 120, Folder 222)
    - Introduction; Management of cancer pain. CV Item 223, 1982. Acta Anaesth. Scand. Suppl. 74, 26:5-10, 75-82. (Box 120, Folder 223)
    - Cancer Pain. Basic considerations. CV Item, 1984. Advances in Pain Research and Therapy, Vol. 7, pp. 529-555. (Box 120, Folder 224)
    - Management of Cancer Pain. CV Item, 1984. Recent Results in Cancer Research 89:13-27. (Box 120, Folder 225)
    - History, Current Status, and Future of Regional Anesthesia. CV Item, 1984. Annales Chirurgiae et Gynaecologiae 73:108-117. (Box 120, Folder 226)
    - Treatment of Cancer Pain. Current Status and Future. CV Item, 1985. Advances in Pain Research and Therapy, Vol. 9, pp. 589-616. (Box 120, Folder 227)
    - History of Pain Concepts and Pain Therapy. CV Item, 1985.. (Box 120, Folder 228)
  - Manuscripts.
    - Pain & Time (Cygnet). File PA1, 20 Jun 1977. For: Film/MS & D. (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Chronic Pain: A Disease State of Major National. File PA2, 30 Jan 1978. For: Bal Harbour Sem. (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - New Information on Pain Mechanisms. File PA3, 30 Jan 1978. For: Bal Harbour Sem. (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Part II: Management of Pain of Advanced Cancer. File PA4, 26 May 1978. For: Venice/Adv. Cancer. (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Nerve Blocks. File PA5, 31 May 1978. For: Venice/Adv. Cancer. (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Role of Nerve Blocks in Cancer Pain. File PA6, 20 Jun 1978. For: Venice/Adv. Cancer. (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Organization & Evaluation of Pain Center. File PA7, 06 Oct 1978. For: Astra Aus-Nz. (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - The Role of the Anes in Mgmt of Pain. File PA8, 06 Oct 1978. For: Astra Aus-Nz. (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Current Status of Pain Therapy. File PA9, 11 Jan 1979. For: NCI. (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Management of Pain. File PA10, 02 Feb 1982. For: Heidelberg. (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Current Status of Postoperative Pain. File PA11, 01 Nov 1982. For: Kyoto. (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Recent Advances in Pain Research and Therapy. File PA12, 02 Nov 1982. For: Miami. (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Basic Principles in the Management of Pain. File PA13, 01 May 1983. For: Manila. (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Role of Nerve Blocks in Acute Cardiac Pain. File PA14, 31 May 1985. For: Rizzi/Vicenza. (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Sympathetic & Sensory Innervation of Vessels in th. File PA15, 31 May 1985. For: Rizzzi/Vicenza. (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Importance and Relevance of the Problem. File PA16, 07 Jun 1985. For: Vincenza. (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - Bone Metastases. File PA17, 12 Dec 1985. For: Rome. (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - Cancer Pain. File PA18, 17 Dec 1985. For: San Francisco. (Box 121, Folder 18)
    - Management of Cancer Pain. File PA19, 18 Dec 1985. For: Budapest. (Box 121, Folder 19)
    - Magnitude of the Problem and the Epidemiology of P. File PA20, 03 Apr 1986. For: NIH. (Box 121, Folder 20)
    - Causalgia & Other Reflex Sympathetic Dystrophy. File PA21, 27 May 1986. For: Madrid. (Box 121, Folder 21)
    - Myofascial Pain Syndromes. File PA22, 27 May 1986. For: Madrid. (Box 121, Folder 22)
    - Wrestling with Pain. File PA23, 19 Jun 1987. For: Venice. (Box 121, Folder 23)
    - Systemic Opioids. File PA24, 19 Jun 1987. For: Venice. (Box 121, Folder 24)
    - Management of Cancer Pain. File PA25, 02 Sep 1987. For: Franklin Gen. Hosp. (Box 121, Folder 25)
    - Management of Postoperative Pain. File PA26, 02 Sep 1987. For: Franklin Gen. Hosp. (Box 121, Folder 26)
    - Cancer Pain Control. File PA27, 13 Oct 1987. For: New York. (Box 121, Folder 27)
    - Pain. File PA28, 11 Dec 1987. For: N.W. University. (Box 121, Folder 28)
    - Pathophysiology Pain. File PA29, 29 Dec 1987. For: A.S.R.A. San Francisco. (Box 121, Folder 29)
    - Future Trends in Pain Therapy. File PA30, 12 Feb 1988. For: A.S.R.A. Williamsburg. (Box 121, Folder 30)
    - Pain Management. File PA31, 20 Jan 1989. For: Portugal. (Box 121, Folder 31)
    - Pain Research & Therapy. File PA32, 20 Jan 1989. For: Oslo. (Box 121, Folder 32)
    - Management of Cancer Pain. File PA33, 07 Aug 1989. For: Franklin Gen. Hosp. (Box 121, Folder 33)
    - Pain Treatment Prog. File PA34, 07 Aug 1989. For: Franklin Gen. Hosp. (Box 121, Folder 34)
    - Postoperative Pain. File PA35, 11 Oct 1989. For: St. Louis. (Box 121, Folder 35)
    - Pain Clinic. File PA36, 05 Jul 1990. For: Japan. (Box 121, Folder 36)
    - Biology Pathophysiology. File PA37, 27 Aug 1990. For: Japan. (Box 121, Folder 37)
    - Hyperalgesia. File PA38, 08 Mar 1991. For: Galveston. (Box 121, Folder 38)
    - Patients with Chronic Pain. File PP1, 29 Jul 1974. For: ? (Box 121, Folder 39)
    - Pain Mechanisms. File PP2, 20 Jan 1975. For: ASA Ref. Course. (Box 121, Folder 40)
    - Organiz. & Function of a Pain Clinic. File PP3, 27 Jan 1975. For: AAAS Symp. (Box 121, Folder 41)
    - Intro: Goals of IASP & World Congress. File PP4, 05 Sep 1975. For: 1st World Congress. (Box 121, Folder 42)
    - International Symos. Cancer Pain. File PP5, 09 Sep 1975. For: HS Press Rel. (Box 121, Folder 43)
    - Introductory Remarks. File PP6, 09 Sep 1975. For: Int. Sym. Cancer. (Box 121, Folder 44)
    - Prob. Pain & Pain Res. (Nat. Adv. Council). File PP7, 18 Nov 1975. For: NIDR. (Box 121, Folder 45)
    - Basic Prin. Managing Chronic Pain. File PP8, 01 Jan 1976. For: Speech/Miami. (Box 121, Folder 46)
    - Rec. Adv. Pain Research. File PP9, 01 Jan 1976. For: Miami. (Box 121, Folder 47)
    - Rec. Adv. Pain. Res. & Ther. File PP10, 04 Feb 1976. For: ? (Box 121, Folder 48)
    - Chronic Pain: Importance & Mechanisms. File PP11, 03 Mar 1976. For: VI Cong./WFSA. (Box 121, Folder 49)
    - Neurophysiologic & Psychologic Substrat. File PP12, 09 Mar 1976. For: VI Cong./WFSA. (Box 121, Folder 50)
    - Nerve Blocks for Pain Res. & Ther. File PP13, 16 Apr 1976. For: ? (Box 121, Folder 51)
    - Introductory Remarks. File PP14, 15 May 1976. For: Nat. Conf. Card. (Box 121, Folder 52)
    - Cancer Pain: A Nat'l Health Prob. File PP15, 28 Jun 1976. For: NCI/CCCGR. (Box 121, Folder 53)
    - Role Anes. in Management of Pain. File PP16, 25 Aug 1976. For: ? (Box 121, Folder 54)
    - Role Anes. Common Cause of Allev. Pain. File PP17, 04 Oct 1976. For: ASA/Wood. (Box 121, Folder 55)
    - Cancer Pain: Nat'l Health Prob (CCCR). File PP18, 08 Nov 1976. For: NCI. (Box 121, Folder 56)
    - Neurophysiologic & Pathologic Aspects. File PP19, 17 Nov 1976. For: Arch Surg 77. (Box 121, Folder 57)
    - Spec. Methods of Cardiac Pain Relief. File PP20, 10 Dec 1976. For: Nat. Conf. Card. (Box 121, Folder 58)
    - Parturition Pain: New Thoughts Pathways. File PP21, 01 Jan 1977. For: Nesacaine. (Box 121, Folder 59)
    - Pref. Pro Dolore "Curr Conc Mgmt Pain". File PP22, 01 Feb 1977. For: Melzack Mtg. (Box 121, Folder 60)